Okay, our XML's looking pretty slick, but
我们的 XML 看起来很整洁
we still have to add the interactivity with Java.
但还需要添加 Java 代码来增加交互性
Now, using the previous exercises as an example,
现在 我们使用之前的练习题当做范例
you're going to make the right side update for team_b.
你要在右边来更新 Team_B
Before doing anything else you're going to copy and paste the code for
在做其他事之前 你需要从讲师注释复制
displayForTeamB from the instructor notes into your own code.
displayForTeamB 的代码 并粘贴到你的代码里
And you're going to update the text view ID for
你还要把 TextView ID 改为
Team B to team_b_score, if you haven't already.
team_b_score 如果你还没有改的话
I'll show you how to do both of these now.
我给你展示一下怎么完成它
All right, here we are in our Java code.
现在我们在你的 Java 代码里
I've got the display for Team B code copied, I'm going to do this right
复制完 displayForTeamB 代码
below, not inside but below, the displayForTeamA and paste.
在 displayForTeamA 下边粘贴 而不是里边
To make it not inside,
为了不粘贴在里边
you want to make sure that it's after this bracket right here.
你要确保粘贴在这个括号后边
And you know that the two curly braces match up because when you put your
你知道的这两个大括号是一对
cursor next to one of the curly braces, the other one highlights.
当你把光标放在一个上边 另一个会变成高亮
Okay, so I've pasted this code here, good.
好的 已经把代码粘过来了
Now I need to go over to my XML code, get rid of the preview, okay.
现在看看 XML 代码 取消预览模式
And I'm going to scroll down to this TextView here, and
往下滑 滑到 TextView 这
I actually already updated this in the last video, but if you need to update
在上一个视频中我已经修改过了 但是如果你想试试
it, I'm going to pretend I didn't, you could type id and set the id attribute.
我可以假装没有修改 你可以输入 id 然后设置相应属性
And remember, you want the @+id/ and then you type the id that you want,
记住 先输入 @+id/ 然后输入你想要的 id
in my case, I want team_b_score, okay, cool.
在这 我想输入 team_b_score
Okay, and now you're pretty much ready to start hooking up the Java.
现在可以关联 Java 了
I'm not going to give you too, too many instructions, but,
我不会给你太多的指导 但是
if you're feeling like you might get stuck, here's some things to consider.
如果你感觉遇到困难了 你就想想这些问题
Think about how you're going to associate the buttons
怎么把按钮和
with running some code in, Java.
在Java 运行的代码相关联
This was one of the first steps we did for the team a side.
这是我们为 A 队做的第一步
Next, consider hat new variable or variables you'll need.
然后想想需要什么新的变量
Hint, you're going to need at least one.
提示一下 你至少需要一个新变量
Finally, think a little bit about what's going to happen when you click
最后想想 当你点击每个按钮后
on each button.
会发生什么
Now, I just want to point out that these steps
我想指出 这些步骤
loosely relate to the steps we used to make the team a side.
与我们之前写的 A 队代码有一定联系
So if you're feeling really, really stuck,
如果你还是不懂
reviewing those videos again might be helpful, and then, once you're done,
再看看这些视频也许会有用 然后 一旦你做完了
you have the satisfaction of checking off this box, okay, get to it.
就可以勾选这个框了 完成